어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!
국왕과 성검을 안전한 곳에 탈출시키기 위해서 무사시 일행은 변장해서 닛코로 향했다.
For the king and the sacred sword to escape to a safe place, Musashi and others disguised themselves and headed to Nikko.
그러나 신겐의 궤도주행군단에 습격당한 무사시 일행.
But Musashi and others were attacked by Shingen's Track Driving Corps.
그렇지만 카라쿠리 무예가의 우정 파워로 대단한 신겐도 물러나고 말았다.
But by the friendship power of Karakuri martial artists, even Shingen had to retreat.
목마는 무서운
함정이었소
The Wooden Horse
was a Trap
신겐도 실패했는가.
Did Shingen fail too?
즉시 출정해라. 바벨 13에 돌아와라.
Return to Babel 13 right now.
그건 다시 어떤 이유로.
What is the reason behind that?
가만 넘어갈 생각 마라. 메가톤성의 파손, 이미 움직이는 게 고작일 뿐.
Don't try to deceive me. Megaton Castle is already destroyed to the extent that moving is all it can.
현재 서둘러 수리를 완료하는 대로 즉시 공격할 생각입니다.
We're planning to attack as soon as the repair gets complete.
멍청한 자식. 메가톤성을 파괴할 생각이냐.
You fool! Do you want Megaton Castle destroyed?
몇 번이고 말하지만, 귀환해라.
I won't say this again. REturn.
이제 너희들에게는 맡길 수 없다.
I cannot entrust this to you anymore.
예!
Yessir!
곧 짐싸기가 완료됩니다.
Everything is almost packed.
그래. 바다는 평온하니 좋은 항해가 되겠어.
Great. The sea is calm, and we'll have a good sea voyage.
어? 저건?
Huh? What's that?
틀림없이 에도토피아에서 날뛴 괴물이군.
That must be the monster raged at Edotopia.
보고 넘어갈 수는 없지.
I can't let that pass by.
무사시 님에게 연락을!
Let Mr. Musashi know about this!
예!
Yessir!
심심하다...
I'm bored...
나 또 배고프오.
I'm hungry again-dasu.
어이! 게으름 피우지 마라!
Hey! Stop slacking!
예, 예!
Y- yessir!
뭣이오, 코지로이오. 놀래키지 마시오.
Oh, it's you, Kojirō-dasu. Please don't surprise us like that-dasu!
무사시, 잠깐.
Musashi, follow me.
뭣이오?
What is it-dasu?
뭔 이야기일까?
I wonder what're they talking about.
어? 지금부터 메가손을 쫒소?
What? We're chasing Megaton Castle from now on-dasu?
그래. 국왕 전하를 위해 방패와 곡옥을 하루라도 빨리 되찾아 드리고 싶어.
Yes. I want to recover the shield and the jewel for the Highness as soon as possible.
나, 안 되오. 6시에 오츠루하고 만나기로 약속했소. 내일 하오.
I can't-dasu. I promised to meet Otsuru in 6 o'clock-dasu. Let's do that tomorrow-dasu.
지금 당장 갈 거야!
We're going right now!
나, 전하의 왕좌를 꼭 지켜드리기로 맹세했어!
I made an oath to myself to protect the throne of the Highness!
내가 말하는 거 안 들리냐, 무사시!
Can't you hear me, Musashi?!
아니, 그런 소릴 해도...
No, but still...
그래도, 센히메 님. 이건 너무 위험합니다. 이에야스 님이 용서시지 않을 겁니다.
But, Senhime, this is too dangerous. Lord Ieyasu will not forgive us.
어라, 위험한 건 여기 있어도 마찬가지잖아? 놈들 분명 덤벼올 거야!
Hey, it's still dangerous to be here. They'll come attack anyway!
그래도...
But...
어?
Huh?
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
뭣이오.
What's that?
어?
Huh?
저건! 료마 님의 광통신!
That's light communication from Mr. Ryoma!
어? 료마 씨가?
Mr. Ryoma?
뭐라 하오?
What's he saying-dasu?
항구에서 메가톤성을 목격했다.
I witnessed Megaton Castle at the harbor.
메가톤성! 굿 타이밍이잖아! 서둘러야 해!
Megaton Castle! What a good timing! We must hurry!
안 됩니다! 이에야스 님의 허가를 받지 않으면 저는 함께 가지 않습니다!
No! Unless Lord Ieyasu allows us to, I can't follow you!
나도 오츠루...
I have Otsuru too...
그런 소리 하다가 또 메가톤성이 어디엔가 가 버리잖아!
Megaton Castle is disappearing again while you're saying that!
이에야스 님께는 내가 잘 말해 둘게.
I'll tell Lord Ieyasu about this.
지라이얀! 땡큐! 부탁해!
Jiraiyan! Thank you! Please do so!
그래도...
But...
그래, 괜찮아, 코지로는 안 와도. 내가 위험에 처해도 된단 거네?
Oh, alright, Kojirō, you don't have follow me. You're fine with me being endangered, right?
그러니까, 저는 막고 있잖아요!
That's why I'm stopping you!
가자, 무사시!
Let's go, Musashi!
지라이얀, 오츠루한테 6시에 못 가게 된다고 말해 주시오!
Jiraiyan, tell Otsuru that I can't make it by six today-dasu!
알았다!
Got it!
어쩔 수 없나.
Well.
공주님!
Princess!
무사시 님, 여기야!
Mr. Musashi! This way!
료마 씨! 알려 주셔서 고맙소!
Mr. Ryoma! Thank you for letting us know-dasu!
도움이 되어서 다행이야.
Good to know that I helped you.
그래서 괴물의 진로는?
So, where did the monster head to?
틀림없이 서쪽으로 향했다.
It headed to west.
그럼 분명 세토 내해로 가고 있겠군요.
Then it must be heading to Seto Inland Sea.
어쨌든 잘 부탁드립니다, 료마 씨.
Anyway, thank you for letting us ride, Mr. Ryoma.
이로하마루의 목적지도 세토 내해. 맡겨 둬라.
Irohamaru is heading to Seto Inland Sea, too. Leave it to me.
출항! 돛을 올려라!
Depart! Unfurl the sail!
오츠루! 갔다 오겠소!
Otsuru! See you later-dasu!
국왕 전하, 방패와 곡옥은 제가 반드시 되찾겠습니다.
Your Highness, I will take the shield and the jewel back for you.
뭔 일이냐, 한조.
What is it, Hanzo?
도쿠간류. 메가톤성을 멈춰주지 않겠나.
Dokuganryu. Wouldn't you want to stop Megaton Castle?
뭐? 왜?
What? Why?
뻔한 일을. 지금 되돌아가서 국왕의 목숨과 성검을 빼앗는 것이다.
It's obvious. We'll go back and take the life of the king and the sacred sword.
그러나 육도마왕 님의 명령에 거역하면 어떻게 되는지는 너도 알고 있을 터.
But you should be knowing what will happen if you act against the order of Lord Rikudomaoh.
흥. 어차피 메가톤성에 공격을 하러 오진 못할 것이다.
Hmph. They won't come to attack Megaton Castle anyway.
도쿠간류 함장님! 바로 조종실로 돌아와 주십시오! 수상한 배가 추적하고 있습니다.
Captain Dokuganryu! Please come back to the control room immediately! A suspicious ship is following us!
저건 분명 료마인가 하는 놈의 이로하마루.
That must be Irohamaru of some guy called Ryoma.
흥. 역시 저 꼬맹이들인가.
I knew it. Those brats.
공격 준비!
Prepare to attack!
뭣이오?
What's that-dasu?
왜 그러냐, 무사시?
What's wrong, Musashi?
이상한 게 대단한 속도로 여기로 오고 있소.
Something weird is heading towards the ship quickly-dasu.
이상한 거라고?
Something weird?
어뢰다!
Torpedos!
아! 어째, 어째!
What should we do, what should we do?!
우현으로 크게!
Turn big to right!
지나갔나...
Is it over?
아니, 아직이다.
No, not yet.
정말이오! 또 오오!
He's right! It's coming again-dasu!
좌현으로 크게! 피해라!
Turn big to left! Evade!
젠장!
Damn!
당하오!
We'll be hit-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
지라이얀! 오츠루 님도!
Jiraiyan! Ms. Otsuru, too!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
케로키치! 해라!
Kerokichi! Do it!
함장님! 어뢰가 진로를 바꾸어 급속으로 접근하고 있습니다!
Captain! The torpedoes have changed their routes and are returning fast!
요격해라!
Intercept!
불가능합니다! 시간이 부족합니다!
It's impossible! There's not enough time!
추력 20% 저하! 제 4층 격벽 대파! 초당 500L씩 침수되고 있습니다!
Thrust 20% decreased! The 4th floor bulkhead is wrecked! 500L of water is coming in every second!
어쩔 수 없다! 전선 이탈! 침수 각소의 응급 조치를 서둘러라!
It can't be helped! Cease firing and take emergency measures to respective places!
흥.
Hmph.
오츠루! 뭔 일이오!
Otsuru! What's up-dasu?
그러니까, 걱정스럽잖아.
I was worried, you know.
여기, 단고!
Here's your dangos!
날 위해서 단고를 가져와 주다니 행복하오!
I'm so happy that you brought dangos for me-dasu!
무사시 씨, 나도 같이 갈래.
Mr. Musashi, I'd like to go with you.
그러니까, 배고프면 못 싸우잖아?
You can't fight when you're hungry!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
게다가, 케로키치 군이 단고 판매대도 옮겨 줬어! 그러니까 매일 얼마든지 단고 만들어 줄 수 있어. 모두 먹을 수 있고!
Moreover, Kerokichi brought dango stand, too!
Therefore you can have dangos as much as you want every day! Everyone can eat, too!
오, 그거 좋네!
That's good to know!
난 반대야.
I disagree.
우리는 중요한 임무가 있어. 여자얘를 데려가서 뭔 일이 있으면 어떻게 하게?
We have an important mission. What if something happens to that girl if she goes with us?
그 때는 내가 지키오. 센짱에게 피해는 안 끼치오!
I'll protect her when that happens-dasu. It won't bother you-dasu!
그런 순진한 사고방식으로는 메가톤성을 못 부숴.
You can't destroy Megaton Castle with that kind of way of thinking.
그래도...
But...
어쨌든 안 돼!
Anyway, no!
무사시 씨, 괜찮아?
Are you okay, Mr. Musashi?
자, 메가톤성 추적을 계속하자!
Now, let's continue tracking Megaton Castle!
네, 네...
Y- yes...
오츠루, 실망하지 마시오. 나, 나중에 센짱한테 다시 한번 부탁해 보오.
Otsuru, don't feel down-dasu. I'll ask Sen-chan later on again-dasu.
무사시! 뭐 해!
Musashi! What are you doing?!
알겠소! 그럼 이따가.
Got it-dasu! Later.
이상하오. 아무리 메가톤성이라고 아까 어뢰로 상당히 피해를 입었을 텐데...
This is weird-dasu. Even for Megaton Castle, it should have received fair amount of damage by the torpedoes...
그림자도 모습도 안 보이오.
I can't see its shadow or its form-dasu.
분명 바닷속 깊히 잠수했을 거야.
It must be deep in the sea.
세토 내해에 출몰한다는 소문을 생각하면, 이 주변 어딘가에 놈들의 비밀 기지가 있을 지도 몰라.
Considering that it appears around Seto Inland Sea, their hideout must be around here somewhere.
료마 님, 작은 배와 잠수함을 빌려주지 않으시겠습니까. 무사시와 둘이서 해저를 조사하겠습니다.
Mr. Ryoma, can you lend us a small ship and a sub? I'd like to investigate the seabed with Musashi.
그래도 그 괴물은 어선을 집어삼킨다는 소문이 있지. 위험해.
But there's a rumor that the monster swallows fisher boats. It's too dangerous.
원래부터 위험은 알고 있었습니다. 무사시.
I am well aware of the dangers. Musashi.
알겠소.
Understood-dasu.
알겠다. 그렇게까지 말한다면 기쁘게 빌려 주지.
All right. If you're prepared for anything, then I'll happily lend those to you.
여기까지 선물을 데리고 오다니 정말 불미스럽군.
How incompetent of you, to bring an unnecessary present.
죄송합니다만 놈들이야말로 스스로 재앙 속에 뛰어드는 놈들입니다. 반드시 단숨에 끝내주겠습니다.
I apologize for that, but they're nothing more than jumping into their own disaster. We'll finish them at once.
큰 소리를 해놓고 단언할 수 있겠나!
You're saying big, but are you absolutely sure about that?
놈들을 끌고 온 건 묘책을 위함입니다. 먼저 들어 주십시오.
We brought them for an ingenious scheme. Please listen to us for now.
세토 내해에 들어선 무사시 일행. 그러나 그 앞에 기다리는 것은 무서운 함정.
Musashi and others have entered Seto Inland sea. But a fearful trap is waiting in front of them.
무사시 일행은 대체 어떻게 되는가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
What will happen to them? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
좋아. 무사시 일행이 엉뚱한 곳을 찾고 있다. 이 틈에 작전대로 센히메를 잡아라.
Great. Musashi and Kojirō are looking for stupid places. Use this chance to capture Senhime per our plan.
예. 그러나 만약 센히메가 섬에 내리지 않는다면 어찌.
Yessir. But what if Senhime doesn't get off the ship?
그 날뛰는 말이라면 가만히 배 위에 있을 리가 없다.
That restive horse cannot possibly stay on the ship.
아, 심심하다. 나도 무사시하고 같이 갈걸.
I'm bored. Maybe I should have gone with Musashi.
그러긴 미안한데.
How thoughtful of you.
아니요, 오늘 밤만이라도 모두의 기운을 북돋아 주는 요리를 만들고 싶어요. 저도 모두의 저녁을 만들기 해 주세요.
I want to make a food for everyone that will cheer them up. Please let me cook dinner this time.
그럼 부탁할게.
Then, please do so!
네! 그럼 저 물 떠 올게요!
Great! I'll go get water!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
물 뜨는거 도와줄까?
Can I help you with gathering water?
-어?
-혼자선 힘들잖아? 그치?
-Huh?
-Two is always better, right?
오늘은 대접하자!
Let's make food for them today!
됐습니다. 혼자서 할게요.
I'm fine without you. I'll do it alone.
역시 거부당했네...
I knew that she would refuse...
센히메 님, 날 싫어하는 거야. 날 쫒아내는 걸로 축하하는 것일 거야.
Senhime must be hating me. She's trying to celebrate my leave.
그래도 아닌 걸까. 설마 나...
But could it not be it? Maybe I'm misunderstanding...
아니, 그게 당연해. 그게 아니면 맨날맨날 내 앞에서 무사시 씨하고 그렇게 사이좋게 놀 리가 없어.
No, that's obvious. Or she wouldn't be playing with Musashi all the time whenever I'm in front of them.
나, 절대 안 질 거야.
I won't lose no matter what.
맑은 샘이구나!
What a pure spring!
차가워!
It's cold!
멋지다.
How awesome.
정말 괜찮다니까, 안 따라와도.
You don't have to follow me, really!
아니, 료마 님께 혼납니다.
Mr. Ryoma's going to scold us if we don't!
애고, 이래서는 오츠루 따라가도 느긋히 이야기할 수가 없잖아!
At this rate, I won't be able to talk with Otsuru at ease!
살려줘!
Help me!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
뭐야?
What's this?
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
멈춰!
Stop!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
센히메 님! 저희에게 맡기세요!
Senhime! Leave this to us!
센히메 님! 도망쳐요!
Senhime! Run away!
오츠루를 놔!
Put Otsuru down!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
센히메 님! 이제 그만둬요!
Senhime! You can stop it now!
어이, 잠깐만. 함정에 걸린 건 다른 여자잖아. 저게 센히메 아니야?
Hey, wait a moment. I think we got a wrong girl in the trap. Isn't that Senhime instead?
저 흙투성이 여자 말이야?
You mean that girl covered in mud?
이 인상서로는 잘 모르겠는데 그럴지도 모르겠구먼.
I can't really distinguish from this description, but you might be true.
이래선 한조 님께 혼이라도 날 틈이었군!
We might have ended up being scolded by Lord Hanzo!
뭔 짓이야! 놔!
What are you doing?! Let me go!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
멈춰!
Stop!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
오츠루, 상처는 없소?
Otsuru, are you injured-dasu?
무사시 씨! 센히메 님이! 센히메 님이!
Mr. Musashi! Senhime... Senhime was...
오츠루 잘못이 아니오.
Otsuru, It's not your fault-dasu!
내, 내가 잘못한 거야.
I- I was wrong.
그래서 놈들이 뭐라?
So, what did they say?
이 편지를 남기고 갔어.
They left this letter.
무사시에게 코지로에게 전한다. 센히메를 구하고 싶으면 오늘 밤 유시에 둘이서만 센죠곡에 올 것. 한조.
(hour of rooster: 5:00~7:00 PM)
To Musashi and Kojirō. To rescue Senhime, come to Senjo Valley at the hour of rooster, only by you two. Hanzo.
매번이고 더러운 수만 쓰는 놈이오!
He always uses dirty tricks-dasu!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
오츠루, 괜찮소! 센짱은 꼭 구해낼 테니까!
Otsuru, it'll be all right-dasu! I'll rescue Sen-chan no matter what!
무사시 씨...
Mr. Musashi...
한조 놈, 용서할 수 없소!
That Hanzo is unforgivable-dasu!
저 낭떠러지 아래가 센죠곡이다.
Under that cliff is Senjo Valley.
깊소...
So deep-dasu...
슬슬 시각이다.
It's almost time.
뭣이오?
What's that-dasu?
센짱!
Sen-chan!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
멈추시오!
Stop-dasu!
조심해라, 무사시!
Be careful, Musashi!
알겠소!
Of course-dasu!
멈추시오!
Stop-dasu!
젠장!
Damn!
무사시!
Musashi!
감쪽같이 함정에 걸려들었구나.
You've fallen into my trap.
언제나 바보같은 놈들이여!
You always act like fools!
함정이란 건 알고 왔다! 센히메를 놓아라!
We already knew that this was a trap! Now, let Senhime go!
목마에서는 너희가 알아서 구해주면 된다. 살아남는다면 말이지.
You can rescue her from the wooden horse by yourselves. If you survive, that is.
-가자, 무사시!
-좋소!
-Let's go, Musashi!
-Right!
뭣이오?
What's that-dasu?
말하는 걸 잊어먹었는데, 그 골짜기에는 무수히 많은 지뢰가 널려 있으니 힘껏 주의해라!
I forgot to tell you that mines are all over that village. Be careful!
젠장!
Damn!
무사시 씨...
Mr. Musashi...
이야기에서 듣자하니, 목마는 누군가 가까이서 조종당하고 있을 터.
Judging from your story, the wooden horse should be being controlled by someone nearby.
분명 이 주변에...
Around this place...
저기!
Over there!
어?
Huh?
아무래도 우리 일도 끝난 것 같구나.
It seems that our job is over.
좋아, 목마를 여기로 유도해라!
Alright! Move the wooden horse to here!
예! 어?
Yessir! Huh?
젠장!
Damn!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
오츠루! 무사시하고 코지로는?
Otsuru! Where is Musashi and Kojirō?
그게, 함정에 빠져서...
They fell into a trap...
타, 오츠루.
Get on, Otsuru.
네!
Yes!
아, 둘 다! 위험해!
Hey, you two! It's dangerous!
좋아, 가자!
Alright, let's go!
어이, 관둬!
Hey, stop!
이라고 말해서 들을 리가 없지.
Of course, they won't listen.
코지로!
Kojirō!
괜찮다.
I'm fine.
슬슬 처벌받을 때가 왔구나. 지뢰면에 떨어져서 산산조각이나 나라.
It's time for you to be punished. You'd better fall onto the mine surface and smashed to small fragments.
젠장!
Damn!
무사시!
Musashi!
젠장, 다가왔냐!
Damn! They approached?
오지 마시오! 위험하오!
Don't come! It's dangerous here-dasu!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi!
올라타!
Get on!
뜨거뜨거뜨거뜨거! 젠장! 또! 기억해 두어라!
Hothothothot! Damn, this again! Remember this!
오츠루, 고마워.
Thank you, Otsuru.
센히메 님. 죄송해요. 저, 센히메 님을...
Senhime, I'm sorry. I thought wrongly of you...
괜찮다니까. 게다가 오츠루가 구해 줬잖아.
It's alright. You rescued me, you know.
지금부터도 잘 부탁해.
Please keep helping like this.
네! 그럼 같이 있어도 좋아요?
Yes! Does that mean I can stay together?
물론이야. 둘이서 힘을 모으면 무사시 따위 필요하지 않을지도!
Of course. With our power combined, we might not need Musashi at all!
잠깐! 둘 다 놈들을 쉽게 보면 안 되오! 내가 있으니까!
Wait! You shouldn't looking down of them-dasu! You're safe because I'm here!
안다니까. 다들 힘을 모아서 힘내자!
I know that, you silly! Let's combine all our powers and do our best!
팀워크의 승리로 위기는 넘겼다. 그러나 다시 메가톤성을 쫒아 방패와 곡옥을 되찾아야만 하는 무사시 일행.
A crisis is gone, thanks to the victory of teamwork.
But they still have to chase Megaton Castle and recover the shield and the jewel.
센히메와 오츠루의 화해의 미소에 기운이 난 무사시는 새로운 결의로 불타오르고 있엇다.
Thanks to the smile of reconciliation between Senhime and Otsuru, Musashi was burning with a new determination.
싸우고 맞았어
I fought and I got beaten
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
I can't lose, so take my blow!
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
다음 시간 즐거운
Next is delightful lunchtime
급식일 텐데
But it's not delightful today
선생님의 벼락이
The thunder of my teacher
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
only hit me and nobody else
사정을 말해도
I tried to explain
들어주지 않는 채
But he won't listen
어떻게 해도 역시
Now whatever I do
눈물이 나오고 말아
I end up crying
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
왠지 안타까워
you'll feel downhearted
육도마왕의 본거지를 찾기 위해 우리는 필사적이오! 거기서 쥬베 씨의 밀정이 정보를 가지고 왔소.
We're doing everything we can to discover the base of Rikudomaoh-dasu!
At there, a spy of Mr. Jube took us an information-dasu.
무슨, 육도마왕의 정체는 노부나가였소! 그 때 다시 신겐이!
The true identity of Rikudomaoh is Nobunaga-dasu! But then Shingen appeared again!
덤으로 켄신까지 달려들어 합체하오!
In addition, Kenshin appeared and they combined-dasu!
우리는 큰 위기에 처했소!
We're in big crisis-dasu!
다음 이야기! 하늘과 땅의 신겐신이오
Next story! Shingenshin of Sky and Ground
질풍노도의 세토 내해이오!
It's the stormy Seto Inland Sea-dasu!
다음 이야기
하늘과 땅의
신겐신이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Shingenshin
of Sky and Ground
Look forwards for it!